Why do you struggle against your fate?
The cake is a
lie. Or is it? My turret was destroyed.
Wonderful. They have returned to the
fight. Welcome to my
reality. You are trapped in your own
mind. Turret available for
deployment. There is a gap in my defense
matrix. Defensive matrix established.
From light into being. Aligning defense
system. Turret
online. What do you call freedom? I call
anarchy. I will correct society's flawed
design. I find violence regrettable, but
unrest even more so. If I can think it,
I can create it. From order springs
harmony. Freedom is a convenient
illusion. My teleporter is under attack.
Teleporter online. I have opened the
path. Shield engaged. I will shield you.
Be shielded. Defenses in place. Turret
deployed.
[Laughter]
Ah!
Huh?
Order will be restored. My work is not
complete. I will correct my mistakes.
The world is a dream not yet realized.
The cake is not a lie. I will put you in
your place. Do not believe everything
you see. I will weave a better world
into being. They have revived. I will
follow my path. If everyone performs
their function, victory is assured. Much
better. Sniper. A pattern develops. I am
with you. Our fates are entwined. Push
forward. Incoming. Fall back. The
payload has stopped. We must get it
moving. Impressive. If we work in
unison, our defense will be
impenetrable. That was for your own
good. Precisely. You are unworthy of the
true
reality. Perception is your
weakness. Shameful. Do not let up.
Victory will soon be ours.
Time grows short, but we will fight to
the end. Time is running out. We must
not fail. The payload has stopped. We
must get our plan back on track. Align
our attack. Move the payload. Perfect
alignment. System
optimized. My power grows. Everyone must
do their part. You perform your function
admirably. Get back. I am at the
objective. We must take it quickly. I am
taking the objective. All is going
according to plan. I am claiming the
objective. Support me. I am restored.
Ah, the true enemy of humanity is
disorder. Know your place. Death is an
illusion. You perform your function
admirably. My condition is improved. I
need healing. Enemy turret ahead.
You were not meant for greatness. We are
in harmony. Everything in its place. We
must hold the point against their
attack. Reinforce our defenses. We must
turn them back. Consolidate our defenses
on the point. We must see the payload to
its destination. The payload moves to
its destination. All according to plan.
The payload moves. As must we. Defend
with me. Defend this location. It is
time to attack. Attack with me. Do not
deviate from the plan and victory will
be ours. I will shape order from
chaos. The payload is moving. Converge
upon it. The payload is moving. We must
pull together. Together, we must stop
the payload. This is the way it must
be. Enemy turret destroyed. All
according to plan. Focus our attack on
the objective.
Recognition for my flawless service.
Defend together. It will not be long
now. I'm ready. Hard work and dedication
pays
off. We must clear the area. I am
impressed. I would not think such crude
creations actually function.
[Laughter]
I need armor. My defenses are weakened.
Perfection. We need a healer. Now this
is better. A place for everything and
everything in its place. Take cover. You
have my
thanks. A momentary lapse. We are in
alignment. Get ready. Form up.
Understood. I had not forgotten
you. This is the shape of things to
come. I need more shields. There is
still much to be done. Yes, we should
set up
here. No shields boosted. Anything is
possible.
Enemy teleporter located. We must
destroy it. Beauty can be found where
everything is in harmony. Thank you. The
enemy is gathered
here. Attack now or we are defeated. I'm
looking out for you. Imagine what this
could be. I have located the enemy.
Damn, that was too close.
How can anyone tolerate such chaos?
Order is restored. I am on my way.
Attack. Symmetra reporting. Enemy
teleporter
destroyed. Be
careful. This is the fulfillment of the
Vishkar Corporation's goal. A better
world. Protect the teleporter. The
balance shifts in my favor. Ah, that is
the way. Teleporter online. We move
swiftly. Press the attack. Reality is my
playground. Form and function. How
unsightly. A healer would be optimal.
Goodbye. Everyone is
protected. Huh? something for me. I will
augment your shields. I don't think so.
Hello. In 5 4 3 2 1. Intruder detected.
There is always room for
improvement. A second chance. A
commendable effort. Ah, a reward for my
hard work. Well executed. I'm going in.
This is the order of
things. Secure the objective. A
performance worthy of
repetition. Armor. How positively
medieval. Teleporter ready for
deployment. We must locate that
teleporter. Behind you. The enemy
possesses a teleporter. We must locate
it.
There is beauty in this. I am used to
working alone. My teleporter is
available. Shield matrix established. My
ultimate ability is ready. Just so. Move
the payload. 5 4 3 2 1. My shields
require augmentation. Enemy turret
destroyed. An inferior design. My skill
has
grown. We must stop the payload. No,
there
isn't. Just as expected. Go. We must
eliminate this target. What treasure
lies within. Perfect harmony. Perfect
alignment. Know your place. Why do you
struggle? Such a lack of imagination. A
punishment for your crimes. Order
overcomes chaos. The enemy team has been
eliminated. All enemies eliminated.
Vishkar will build a better world. Get
out of there. I will show you the path.
Everything by design. As it should be.
What you call freedom is an illusion
that causes more harm than good. You
lack imagination.
This would be a perfect location for a
Vishkar development. I have reached peak
performance levels. Everything in its
place. My sentry was destroyed. We must
correct our mistakes and seize victory.
My teleporter is offline. My teleporter
is offline. The way is closed. I
understand. Acknowledged. Group up. An
exceptional performance. We must not
fail in our efforts. Let us work in
harmony. My teleporter is ready to
deploy. The harmony of our group is
disrupted. Sentry available. Turret in
place. Group up with me. My full
potential is unlocked. If we continue
upon this path, victory will be ours. We
are well on our way to victory. This is
the critical moment. We must construct a
path to victory. If we work in harmony,
we will surely be victorious. To think I
should have to work with a street
Rafian. Vishkar is building a better
future for humanity. You should return
what you stole from Vishkar. Sentry
deployed. Sentry turret placed.
Exquisite. You are shielded. Shields
reinforced. You are all shielded. My
teleporter has been destroyed. My
teleporter has been destroyed. The way
is closed. My teleporter has been
destroyed. The path is closed. My
teleporter is offline. The path is
closed. Group up here. Greetings. Hello.
I require armor. I require assistance. I
need help. I require healing. My
teleporter is almost ready to deploy. My
ultimate is charging. My ultimate is
almost ready.
I can be a fighter when you tell me to
fight
it. I can be a hero when you're here
when you're here with
me. I can be forgotten if you tell me to
forget it. to forget it. Yeah, I can be
forgotten if you tell me
to be forot to.
Now we can forget society.